Map Collection Master Index
Avon Free Public Library
Map Collection Master Index
1829-2000
Avon Free Public Library
FA003
12 lf; 1 Map Cabinet
This index lists the 170+ maps in the Marian Hunter History Room of the Avon Free Public Library. The maps cover the years 1625 until the early 2000's. The maps were created between 1829 to the early 2000's.
Restrictions
This collection is open and available for research. Please contact the reference department at the Avon Free Public Library before visiting to ensure that staff is available and materials are ready. https://avonctlibrary.info/services/history-room
Biography
This index lists the 170+ maps in the Marian Hunter History Room of the Avon Free Public Library. The maps cover the years 1625 until the early 2000's. The maps were created between 1829 to the early 2000's. The collection was created by staff members from multiple donations.
Scope and Content of Collection
This index lists the 170+ maps in the Marian Hunter History Room of the Avon Free Public Library. Each map is numbered; the number corresponds to the description listed in the index. Maps are shelved in the map cabinet in the Marian Hunter History Room unless otherwise indicated.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
United States- Connecticut - Avon
Separated Material
Map 000, Surveyor's Map, 1881 is stored in the Archive Room due to its size.
- Inventory
  - Surveyor's Map, 1881; Author/Creator: Chente Burr; Dimensions: 41.5x21.75; B/W; Notes: in archive room (Item 000)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 2008; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 18.75x13.5; B/W (Item 001)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 2007; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 18.5x17; Color (Item 002)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 2007; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 18.5x17; Color (Item 003)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 2003; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 18.5x17; Color (Item 004)
  - Illustrated City Information Guide, 1998; Author/Creator: Towne Crier Mtg Gro; Dimensions: 26.5x38.5; Color (Item 005)
  - Illustrated City Information Guide, 1998; Author/Creator: Towne Crier Mtg Gro; Dimensions: 26.5x38.5; Color (Item 006)
  - Illustrated City Information Guide, 1998; Author/Creator: Towne Crier Mtg Gro; Dimensions: 26.5x38.5; Color (Item 007)
  - Illustrated City Information Guide, 1998; Author/Creator: Towne Crier Mtg Gro; Dimensions: 26.5x38.5; Color (Item 008)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1998; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 18.5x17; Color; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 009)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1998; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 18.5x17; Color (Item 010)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1998; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 18.5x17; Color (Item 011)
  - Corridor Management and Improvement Base Plan, 1998; Author/Creator: Cap. Reg.Council of Gov.and CT. D.O.T; Dimensions: 22x36; B/W (Item 012)
  - Route 44 Corridor Alternative Studies, 1997; Author/Creator: Cap.Reg.Council of Gov.andCT.D.O.T.; Dimensions: 17x11; B/W (Item 013)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1996; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 18.5x17; Color; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 014)
  - Living Museum of Avon, 1994; Author/Creator: A. August; Dimensions: 24x18; B/W; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 015)
  - Farmington Valley West Hartford Area, 1992; Author/Creator: Cdy Cooper; Dimensions: 21.5x29; B/W; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 016)
  - Farmington Valley West Hartford Area, 1992; Author/Creator: Cdy Cooper; Dimensions: 21.5x29; B/W; Notes: only Colors purple/white (Item 017)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1992; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 17x18.5; Color (Item 018)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1992; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 17x18.5; Color (Item 019)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1990; Author/Creator: Harbor Publications; Dimensions: 18.5,x17; Color; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 020)
  - Life the Farmington River Valley, 1960; Author/Creator: Farmington RiverWatershed; Dimensions: 14x22.5; B/W (Item 021)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1987; Author/Creator: Tom Tarrant Jr. and Co.; Dimensions: 18.5x17; Color (Item 022)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1978; Author/Creator: Tom Tarrant Jr. and Co.; Dimensions: 18.5x17; Color (Item 023)
  - Street of Avon, 1986; Author/Creator: The TR Preston Co. Realtors; Dimensions: 17.5x23; Color; Notes: only Colors red/white (Item 024)
  - Street of Avon, 1986; Author/Creator: The TR Preston Co. Realtors; Dimensions: 17.5x23; Color; Notes: only Colors red/white (Item 025)
  - Street of Avon, 1986; Author/Creator: The TR Preston Co. Realtors; Dimensions: 17.5x23; Color (Item 026)
  - Street of Avon, 1982; Author/Creator: Avon Chamber of Commerce; Dimensions: 22x17.5; Color; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 027)
  - Avon Connecticut, 1984; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 22x17; Color; Notes: * drawer 2 # 32 (Item 028)
  - Avon Connecticut, 1984; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 22x17; Color; Notes: * drawer 2 # 33 (Item 029)
  - Avon Connecticut, 1984; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 22x17; Color; Notes: only Colors red/white (Item 030)
  - Avon Connecticut, 1984; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 22x17; Color; Notes: only Colors red/white (Item 031)
  - Sketches of the Farmington Valley, 1983; Author/Creator: Harriet V. Fox, Alligator Publishg; Dimensions: 23x28; B/W; Notes: * drawer 2 # 36 (Item 032)
  - Sketches of the Farmington Valley, 1983; Author/Creator: Harriet V. Fox, Alligator Publishg; Dimensions: 23x28; B/W; Notes: * drawer 2 # 37 (Item 033)
  - Streets of Avon, 1982; Author/Creator: Avon Chamber of Commerce; Dimensions: 22x17.5; B/W; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 034)
  - Streets of Avon, 1982; Author/Creator: Avon Chamber of Commerce; Dimensions: 22x17.5; Color; Notes: only Colors blue/white (Item 035)
  - Streets of Avon, 1982; Author/Creator: Avon Chamber of Commerce; Dimensions: 22x17.5; B/W; Notes: * drawer 2 # 34 (Item 036)
  - Streets of Avon, 1982; Author/Creator: Avon Chamber of Commerce; Dimensions: 22x17.5; B/W; Notes: * drawer 2 # 35 (Item 037)
  - Zoning Map, 1981; Author/Creator: Planng and Zoning Commission; Dimensions: 23 X 17.5; B/W (Item 038)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1980; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 14.5x21.5; Color (Item 039)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1980; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 14.5x21.5; Color (Item 040)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1980; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 14.5x21.5; Color; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 041)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1980; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 14.5x21.5; Color; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 042)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1980; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 14.5x21.5; Color; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 043)
  - Avon Connecticut Mail-a-Map, 1980; Author/Creator: New Directions Inc.; Dimensions: 14.5x21.5; Color; Notes: only Colors green/white (Item 044)
  - Master sewer plan, 1978; Author/Creator: Kulio Loureiro; Dimensions: 42x30; Color (Item 045)
  - Avon Street Guide, 1976; Author/Creator: Attention Advertisg; Dimensions: 18.5x25; Color (Item 046)
  - Avon Street Guide, 1976; Author/Creator: Attention Advertisg; Dimensions: 18.5x25; Color (Item 047)
  - Historic Site Plan (1979), 1975; Author/Creator: Cap. Region Council of Governments; Dimensions: 3ftx2ft; B/W (Item 048)
  - Historic Site Plan (1979), 1975; Author/Creator: Cap. Region Council of Governments; Dimensions: 3ftx2ft; B/W; Notes: only Colors purple/white (Item 049)
  - Streets of Avon, 1974; Dimensions: 22x17; B/W (Item 050)
  - Shoppers Guide to Avon, 1973; Author/Creator: Avon Chamber of Commerce; Dimensions: 19x25; Color; Notes: published 1988/created 1960 (Item 051)
  - Shoppers Guide to Avon, 1973; Author/Creator: Avon Chamber of Commerce; Dimensions: 19x25; Color; Notes: only Colors purple/white (Item 052)
  - Shoppers Guide to Avon, 1973; Author/Creator: Avon Chamber of Commerce; Dimensions: 19x25; Color (Item 053)
  - Geo.Map of Avon quadrangle, CT: Surficial geology, 1957-1958; Author/Creator: Robert W. Schnabel; Dimensions: 49.5x30; Color; Notes: revised 1984 (Item 054)
  - Geo.Map of Avon quadrangle, CT: Bedrock geology, 1957-1958; Author/Creator: Robert W. Schnabel; Dimensions: 49.5x30; Color; Notes: revised 1984 (Item 055)
  - Revised Zoning Map, 1958; Author/Creator: Technical Planng Associates; Dimensions: 28x39; Color (Item 056)
  - Geo.Map of Avon quadrangle, CT: Bedrock geology, 1957-1958; Author/Creator: R. W. Schnabel; Dimensions: 48.5x29.5; Color (Item 057)
  - U.S. Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; Author/Creator: U.S. Geological Survey; Dimensions: 22,x26.5; Color (Item 058)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; Author/Creator: U.S. Geological Survey; Dimensions: 22x2603; Color; Notes: revised 1984 (Item 059)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; Author/Creator: U.S. Geological Survey; Dimensions: 22x26.5; B/W; Notes: revised 1984 (Item 060)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; Author/Creator: U.S. Geological Survey; Dimensions: 22x27.5; Color; Notes: revised 1984 (Item 061)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; Author/Creator: U.S. Geological Survey; Dimensions: 22x26.5; Color; Notes: revised 1984 (Item 062)
  - U.S. Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; Author/Creator: U.S. Geological Survey; Dimensions: 22x26.5; Color; Notes: revised 1984 (Item 063)
  - U.S. Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; Author/Creator: U.S. Geological Survey; Dimensions: 22x26.5; Color; Notes: revised 1984 (Item 064)
  - U.S. Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; Author/Creator: U.S. Geological Survey; Dimensions: 22x27; Color; Notes: only Colors blue/white (Item 065)
  - Town of Avon Zoning Map, 1951; Author/Creator: Merton Hodge; Dimensions: 21.5x16.5; B/W; Notes: only Colors blue/white (Item 066)
  - Mail-a-Map of Avon, 1959; Author/Creator: J. W. Cooley; Dimensions: 14.5x17; B/W (Item 067)
  - Plan and Profile of Sewage Force, 1946; Author/Creator: Frederick H. Beckwith; Dimensions: 37x22; Color (Item 068)
  - Towpath School Grounds Plan, 1946; Author/Creator: Frederick H. Beckwith; Dimensions: 14x27; Color; Notes: only Colors blue/white (Item 069)
  - Hartford County Rural Delivery Routes, 1942; Dimensions: 47x37; Color (Item 070)
  - Comp.Aerial Survey of the Ensign Bickford Co. Avon Plan, 1930; Author/Creator: Curtis Wright Flyg Service; Dimensions: 10x9.25; B/W (Item 071)
  - 1924 Survey, Dimensions: 17x77; B/W; Notes: reprted 1899 (Item 072)
  - Land of Nod Addition, 1929; Author/Creator: John T. Henderson; Dimensions: 18x24; B/W (Item 073)
  - Secret Lake, circa 1962; Dimensions: 24x32; B/W (Item 074)
  - Land of Nod, 1928; Author/Creator: John T. Henderson; Dimensions: 2ftx3ft; B/W; Notes: only Colors blue/white (Item 075)
  - Land of Nod, 1928; Author/Creator: John T. Henderson; Dimensions: 2ftx3ft; B/W (Item 076)
  - Map of Lots: Secret Lake Drive, 1937; Dimensions: 12.5x44; B/W (Item 077)
  - Secret Lake, 1928; Dimensions: 24xq8; B/W; Notes: revised 1929 (Item 078)
  - Right of Way Map Town of Avon, 1928; Author/Creator: Taylor; Dimensions: 22.5x36; B/W (Item 079)
  - Right of Wayand Track Map Town of Avon, 1915; Dimensions: 55x24; Color; Notes: reprted 1925 (Item 080)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1889-1890; Author/Creator: Henry Gannet, Marcus Baker; Dimensions: 16x20; Color (Item 081)
  - U. S. Geological Survey, 1889-1890; Author/Creator: Chas. Walcott, Henry Gannet, Marcus Baker; Dimensions: 16x20; Color (Item 082)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1800s; Dimensions: 21x15; B/W (Item 083)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1800s; Dimensions: 24x15; B/W (Item 084)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1800s; Dimensions: 24x15; B/W (Item 085)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1800s; Dimensions: 24x15; B/W (Item 086)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 13.5x17.5; Color (Item 087)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 13.5x17.5; Color (Item 088)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 13.5x17; Color (Item 089)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 18x14.5; Color (Item 090)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 15x18; Color (Item 091)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 15x18; Color (Item 092)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 15x18; Color (Item 093)
  - Old Farms Road, 1976; Dimensions: 8x14; B/W (Item 094)
  - Avon, 1975; Author/Creator: Cap. Region Council of Governments; Dimensions: 17x11; B/W (Item 095)
  - Town of Avon Map of School Districts, 1932; Dimensions: 12x16; B/W (Item 096)
  - Town of AvonMap of School Districts, 1932; Dimensions: 17x11; B/W (Item 097)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 21.5x15; B/W (Item 098)
  - Farmington, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 8.5x11; B/W (Item 099)
  - Atlas of Hartford County, 1931; Author/Creator: Dolph and Stewart; Dimensions: 8.5x11; B/W (Item 100)
  - Atlas of Hartford County, 1931; Author/Creator: Dolph and Stewart; Dimensions: 8.5on.x11; B/W (Item 101)
  - Avon Business Directory, 1869; Author/Creator: Baker and Tilden; Dimensions: 15x18; Color (Item 102)
  - Avon 1869, undated; Dimensions: 18.5x24; Color (Item 103)
  - 1855 Hartford County Map, Dimensions: 8.5x11; B/W (Item 104)
  - Hartford 1640, undated; Author/Creator: William S. Porter; Dimensions: 13.5x11; B/W (Item 105)
  - Map of Farmington and Avon, 1850; Dimensions: 13.25x; B/W (Item 106)
  - Map of Farmington and Avon, 1850; Dimensions: 14x19; B/W (Item 107)
  - Map of Farmington and Avon, 1850; Dimensions: 14x17.5; B/W (Item 108)
  - Map of Farmington Valley, 1800s; Dimensions: 18x12; Color (Item 109)
  - Map of Farmington and Avon, 1850; Dimensions: 14x8.5; B/W (Item 110)
  - Avon, 1850; Author/Creator: Eugene Hawley; Dimensions: 14x8.5; B/W (Item 111)
  - Avon, 1850; Author/Creator: Eugene Hawley; Dimensions: 14x8.5; B/W (Item 112)
  - Avon, 1850; Author/Creator: Eugene Hawley; Dimensions: 14x8.5; B/W (Item 113)
  - Avon, 1850; Author/Creator: Eugene Hawley; Dimensions: 14x8.5; B/W (Item 114)
  - Avon, 1850; Author/Creator: Eugene Hawley; Dimensions: 14x8.5; B/W (Item 115)
  - The Farmington Canal 1840, Author/Creator: Eric Sloane; Dimensions: 8.5x11 (Item 116)
  - Specifications of a canal, 1840; Author/Creator: Eric Sloane; Dimensions: 11.5x7; B/W (Item 117)
  - Avon 1830, 1980; Author/Creator: Gladys August, D. Anderson, M. Hunter; Dimensions: 14.5x12; B/W (Item 118)
  - Avon 1830, 1980; Author/Creator: Gladys August, D. Anderson, M. Hunter; Dimensions: 15x11; B/W; Notes: only Colors purple/white (Item 119)
  - Avon 1830, 1980; Author/Creator: Gladys August, D. Anderson, M. Hunter; Dimensions: 13x11.5; B/W (Item 120)
  - Avon 1830, 1980; Author/Creator: Gladys August, D. Anderson, M. Hunter; Dimensions: 22.5x16; B/W (Item 121)
  - Avon Houses 1830, undated; Dimensions: 25x20; B/W (Item 122)
  - Avon Houses 1830, undated; Dimensions: 25x20; B/W (Item 123)
  - An Avon Story, 1980; Author/Creator: Gladys August, D. Anderson, M. Hunter; Dimensions: 27x23; B/W (Item 124)
  - An Avon Story, 1980; Author/Creator: Gladys August, D. Anderson, M. Hunter; Dimensions: 27x23; B/W (Item 125)
  - An Avon Story, 1980; Author/Creator: Gladys August, D. Anderson, M. Hunter; Dimensions: 27x23; B/W (Item 126)
  - An Avon Story, 1980; Author/Creator: Gladys August, D. Anderson, M. Hunter; Dimensions: 27x23; B/W (Item 127)
  - Farmington Center Feeder Canal, undated; Dimensions: 23x18; B/W (Item 128)
  - Feeder Canal, undated; Dimensions: 23.5x17; B/W (Item 129)
  - Aqueduct Avon Map #1, undated; Dimensions: 23x18; B/W (Item 130)
  - Avon - Farmington Aqueduct, undated; Dimensions: 24x20; B/W (Item 131)
  - Map of the Farmington Canal, 1837; Author/Creator: Henry Farnam; Dimensions: 23x18; B/W (Item 132)
  - Map of Farmington, 1829; Dimensions: 20.5x17; B/W (Item 133)
  - Avon Map, undated; Dimensions: 24x19.5; B/W (Item 134)
  - Map of the Farmington Canal, 1837; Author/Creator: Henry Farnam; Dimensions: 15x22; B/W (Item 135)
  - Simsbury South End, 1837; Author/Creator: Henry Farnam; Dimensions: 23x17.5; B/W (Item 136)
  - Simsbury North End, 1837; Author/Creator: Henry Farnam; Dimensions: 23x18; B/W (Item 137)
  - Simsbury South End, 1837; Author/Creator: Henry Farnam; Dimensions: 22.5x15.5; B/W (Item 138)
  - Simsbury North End, 1837; Author/Creator: Henry Farnam; Dimensions: 22x15.5; B/W (Item 139)
  - Simsbury North End, 1837; Author/Creator: Henry Farnam; Dimensions: 20x24.5; B/W (Item 140)
  - Farmington Canal 1828-1847, 2000; Author/Creator: Carl E.Walter/Ruth Sharp Hummel; Dimensions: 25.25x40; Color (Item 141)
  - Connecticut 1735, undated; Dimensions: 30.5x23; Color; Notes: only Colors purple/white (Item 142)
  - Map Showing the First Subdivision of Avon, 1969; Author/Creator: Avon Engeerg Dept.; Dimensions: 36.5x30; Color (Item 143)
  - Map Showing the First Subdivision of Avon, 1969; Author/Creator: Avon Engeerg Dept.; Dimensions: 43.5x36; B/W (Item 144)
  - Map Showing the First Subdivision of Avon, 1969; Author/Creator: Avon Engeerg Dept.; Dimensions: 43.5x36; Color (Item 145)
  - An Exact Map of New England and New York, 1976; Author/Creator: Stephen R. Hayes; Dimensions: 20.75x17; Color (Item 146)
  - Map of Simsbury Connecticut, 1935; Author/Creator: William Floyd Hamilton; Dimensions: 25x32; Color (Item 147)
  - Map of CT showing Principal Highways and Hist. References, 1935; Author/Creator: The Aetna Casualty and Surety Co.; Dimensions: 31.25x18; Color (Item 148)
  - Map of CT showing Principal Highways and Hist. References, 1935; Author/Creator: The Aetna Casualty and Surety Co.; Dimensions: 31.25x18; Color (Item 149)
  - The Story of one corner of CT 16 maps, undated; Author/Creator: Mystic River Historical Society; Dimensions: varies; B/W; Notes: includes 1620, 1625, 1677, 1777, 1781, 1833, 1851, 1854, 1868, 1935 (Item 150)
  - Map of Avon and Canton with street index, undated; Dimensions: 18 X 23.5; Color (Item 151)
  - Map of Air Raid Sector, undated; Author/Creator: SNET Telephone Company and Town of Avon; Dimensions: 29 x 14.5; Color (Item 152)
  - Map of Connecticut Indian Trails, Villages, 1976; Author/Creator: Stephen R. Hayes; Dimensions: 18.75x15; Color; Notes: in archive room (Item 153)
  - Map of Connecticut Indian Trails, Villages, 1976; Author/Creator: Stephen R. Hayes; Dimensions: 19.5x15.25; Color (Item 154)
  - CT State Highway Dept Right of Way Map, 1928; Author/Creator: Charles F. Taylor; Dimensions:; Color (Item 155)
  - CT State Highway Dept Right of Way Map, 1937; Author/Creator: John A. MacDonald; Dimensions:; Color (Item 156)
  - Land and houses owned by the Derrin Family, undated; Dimensions: 8.5x11; B/W (Item 157)
  - The first subdivision of Avon, 1969; Author/Creator: Edward Rueben of Merton Hodge Assoc.; Dimensions: 42 x37.5; Color (Item 158)
  - Nod Division East, 1969; Author/Creator: Edward Rueben of Merton Hodge Assoc.; Dimensions: 31x13; Color (Item 159)
  - New Road, District #6 and #4, undated; Dimensions: 8.5x14; B/W (Item 160)
  - Main Street-Route 44, District #5, 2, 3, 7, 1, 1976; Author/Creator: Avon Historical Society; Dimensions: 8.5x14; B/W (Item 161)
  - Montevideo Road, District #5, 2, 1, 1976; Author/Creator: Avon Historical Society; Dimensions: 8.5x14; B/W (Item 162)
  - Orchard Street, District #6 and 4, undated; Dimensions: 8.5x14; B/W (Item 163)
  - Waterville Road, District #5, 2, 3, 1, undated; Dimensions: 8.5x14; B/W (Item 164)
  - Map No. 16 Generalized Land Use, 1991; Author/Creator: Avon Planning Department; Dimensions: 32x22; Color (Item 165)
  - Town of Avon, undated; Dimensions: 34x42; Color (Item 166)
  - West Avon and Avon Cemetery War Veterans Graves, undated; Author/Creator: Charles R. Hale; Dimensions: 25x7.5; Color (Item 167)
  - West Avon, Avon, and Cider Brook Cemetery War Veterans Graves, undated; Author/Creator: Charles R. Hale; Dimensions: 22x18; B/W (Item 168)
  - West Avon, Avon, and Cider Brook Cemetery War Veterans Graves, 1933; Author/Creator: Charles R. Hale; Dimensions: 21.5x18.5; B/W (Item 169)
  - Greenwood and St. Mary's Cemetery War Veterans Graves, 1933; Author/Creator: Charles R. Hale; Dimensions: 21.5x17.5; B/W (Item 170)
  - Greenwood and St. Mary's Cemetery War Veterans Graves, 1933; Author/Creator: Charles R. Hale; Dimensions: 21.5x16; B/W (Item 171)
  - Greenwood and St. Mary's Cemetery, West Avon, Avon, and Cider Brook Cemetery War Veterans Graves, 1933; Author/Creator: Charles R. Hale; Dimensions: 21.5x16.5; B/W (Item 172)